<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="stones">
        <item>Animal-chicken</item>
        <item>Animal-zebra</item>
        <item>Animal-camel</item>
        <item>Animal-cat</item>
        <item>Animal-hippo</item>
        <item>Animal-lion</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="details">
        <item>The chicken (Gallus domesticus) is a large and round short-winged bird, domesticated from the red junglefowl of Southeast Asia around 8,000 years ago. Most chickens are raised for food, providing meat and eggs; others are kept as pets or for cockfighting.</item>
        <item>Zebras (US:/ˈziːbrəz/, UK: /ˈzɛbrəz, ˈziː-/)[2] (subgenus Hippotigris) are African equines with distinctive black-and-white striped coats. There are three living species</item>
        <item>A camel (from Latin: camelus and Greek: κάμηλος (kamēlos) from Ancient Semitic: gāmāl[7][8]) is an even-toed ungulate in the genus Camelus that bears distinctive fatty deposits known as "humps" on its back. Camels have long been domesticated and, as livestock, they provide food (camel milk and meat) and textiles (fiber and felt from camel hair).</item>
        <item>The cat (Felis catus), also referred to as domestic cat or house cat, is a small domesticated carnivorous mammal. It is the only domesticated species of the family Felidae</item>
        <item>The hippopotamus (Hippopotamus amphibius) (/ˌhɪpəˈpɒtəməs/; pl.: hippopotamuses; also shortened to hippo (pl.: hippos), further qualified as the common hippopotamus, Nile hippopotamus, or river hippopotamus, is a large semiaquatic mammal native to sub-Saharan Africa.</item>
        <item>The lion (Panthera leo) is a large cat of the genus Panthera, native to Africa and India. It has a muscular, broad-chested body; a short, rounded head; round ears; and a dark, hairy tuft at the tip of its tail. It is sexually dimorphic; adult male lions are larger than females and have a prominent mane.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>